And I got to experience Palestine, not just as the place that my family was from, I got to experience oppression.
Like I remember going to visit my uncle in a prison and someone having to explain to me, oh, well, your uncle was in a group of men and then the IDF came and they detained them all.
And then my uncle was in this what they call arbitrary detention where they just could make it up as they go along.
People are not often charged with crimes. And it's like and so even as a young child going to Palestine, I was like, this is not right.
And then my mom had to sit me down and be like, let's explain what's going on here.
Why are there soldiers here? Why is there an occupation? What happened?
What's the. So I got to learn my lineage and my story.
And then I was able to be the person in the U.S. that invoked my Palestinianness, which is what my parents taught us to be.
They said, if anybody asks you where you're from, yes, you're born and raised in Brooklyn, but you are Palestinian.
And I think that's part of it. That coupled with being the oldest child, that being coupled with being a child of immigrants.
I'm always 10 toes down every time, everywhere, every place. You could always count on me in that space.
And that's kind of how I'm known in the movement.